[EP07]
Waiter!
Is this a classic novel plot?
A graceful rejection, huh?
Let's celebrate.
Survived a disaster, after all.
Didn't you say you'd tell me the truth about the Sus?
You haven't thanked me for what I did before.
Fine.
Drink my wine,
and you'll have to go on a date with me.
[The truth behind the investigation of the Su family.]
[Through him,]
[we might be able to find out.]
You bought me a drink.
I'll return it with three drinks.
The first one,
Corpse Reviver.
Resurrection of the Dead.
It's to thank you for that drink.
The second one,
Angel's Kiss.
Thanks for your help.
I've helped you many times.
Which time
does this drink thank?
The one you gave me,
Yunnan Baiyao.
Ah.
This third drink,
Horse's Neck.
Golden Horse's Neck.
It symbolizes honesty,
keeping one's word.
So,
what happened to the Su family?
This romantic moment
seems not the right time to talk about this.
Xiao Wan,
you seem truly different from before.
I'm falling for you more and more.
Then tell me the truth about what happened to the Su family.
and help me find my mom.
You don't want to?
Are you afraid of Ling Shenxing?
Come to me when you get
news about the Sus.
I really like your performance.
It makes me feel
that it's worth coming here tonight.
I'm
getting more and more interested in you.
But it's a pity.
Come here.
Go home with me.
Miss, run!
The Young Marshal wants to put you in jail.
Leave me alone.
Your family didn't hide any prohibited drugs.
It was all his plan.
Take him down!
Go!
As long as you sacrifice yourself
and make everything a secret,
I won't hurt Su Muwan.
How to do it?
It's up to you.
Ling Shenxing always shoots.
Luckily, I ran fast.
Where is this?
Your home.
You told me
to take you to meet your mother.
My mother came home.
[Why didn't Ling Shenxing tell me?]
Mom.
You got hurt a few days ago.
Did you apply the medicine properly?
Are you feeling better?
Mom, why did you hit me?
Young Master Chu,
this is the inner hall of the Su Family.
It's not appropriate for you to be here.
Zhao Yue,
Show him out.
Young Master Chu,
this way please.
Wait.
I'll take care of everything.
Wan'er,
now that you've married into the Ling family,
the affairs of the Su family are no longer your concern.
Mother,
why do you say that?
How could the Su family not be related to me?
Madam,
Young Marshal Ling is waiting
at the gate with his men.
Mother.
Mom.
Young Marshal,
I'm sorry I didn't greet you.
This unfilial daughter
enjoys herself in the Ling family,
leaving us to die.
Take your wife and leave.
I have nothing
to say to you.
My lady.
Mom,
what's going on?
We deserve this
for hiding illegal drugs.
But Xing,
this must come to an end.
Let's call it a day.
Mom.
Young Marshal.
Ling Shenxing,
ask yourself,
did the Su family
really have banned drugs,
or did you set us up
and frame us?
Why did you
You made us suffer so much.
We just want to live a happy life.
Did Chu Nanfeng tell you that?
Do you believe him so much?
Oh, no.
It's on fire.
The Old Lady is still inside.
The windows and doors are sealed from the inside.
She doesn't plan to come out alive.
What did you say?
Let go of me!
Mom!
Hurry!
Come on!
Go!
Be careful!
Don't, Mom!
No!
Mom!
Live well.
Why do you leave me in this way again?
Go in and put out the fire.
The fire is too big.
Mom
We can't get in at all.
Miss
Su Muwan
You still have me.
Mom!
Wan.
Brother.
Why did mom commit suicide?
What's going on?
I'm also investigating the cause of mom's death.
Hongxiu.
Hongxiu might know something.
She's been kidnapped by Ling Shenxing.
I'll go save her.
Wan.
Hongxiu seems to know some secrets.
There are killers looking for her.
She's safer with Ling Shenxing.
Right.
I can't protect her now.
You're poisoned.
It's Ghost Vine,
a chronic poison.
Long-term use causes memory loss
and cause mental confusion.
A faint bitter taste.
Although this prescription includes many spices and hawthorn to disguise it,
although this prescription includes many spices and hawthorn to disguise it,
the taste
is different from ordinary tonics.
Ghost Vine?
What does Ghost Vine taste like?
Ghost Vine has a bitter taste,
and often requires a large amount of spices to disguise it.
That's it.
It's in the tonic.
Be extra careful
with your diet.
The enemy is lurking in the dark,
and we are in the light.
Now that you're married,
I can't
always be there for you
and protect you
like before.
Keep this set of
this set of silver needles.
Make sure to test
everything you eat
or drink
from now on.
Yes.
And this.
Keep it for self-defense.
You have to learn to protect yourself.
It would have been better
if you had listened to me and married
His family is clean,
and he's a nice guy.
Then,
I can
visit you more often.
Unlike now,
I can only...